Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Addition, 2004 [A2004-19] (Box 60)
  - Faculty and staff (Box 60)
    - Bilpuch, Edward G. [Physics; Triangle Universities Nuclear Lab] (Box 63)
    - Bindewald, Richard Andrew [Business and Finance] (Box 63)
    - Binkley, Daniel E. [Forestry] (Box 63)
    - Bird, Warren Phillip [Duke Medical Library] (Box 63)
    - Birkhead, Clarence [Duke Police] (Box 63)
    - Bissett, Garth [Psychoneuroendrocrinology Lab] (Box 63)
    - Biswas, Mrinmay "Moy" [Civil and Environmental Engineering] (Box 63)
    - Bittikorer, John Arthur [Clinical Chemistry] (Box 63)
    - Black, Martin Lee, Jr. [Accounting] (Box 63)
    - Blackburn, Charles [P.R. DUMC] (Box 63)
    - Blackburn, John Oliver [Economics; Provost; Chancellor] (Box 63)
    - Blackburn, William [English] (Box 63)
    - Blackmon, Lillian [Pediatrics] (Box 63)
    - Blackshear, Perry Justin [Endocrinology] (Box 63)
    - Blackwell, Kimberly [Oncology] (Box 63)
    - Blake, Robert Lincoln [Medical Illustration] (Box 63)
    - Blakely, Florence Ella [Perkins Library], Retired 1987 (Box 63)
    - Bland, Kalman P. [Religion Dept.] (Box 63)
    - Blaney, Bernie [Alumnus; Football] (Box 63)
    - Blazer, Dan German [Psychiatry; Medical Education] (Box 63)
    - Bliss, Donald B. [Mechanical Engineering and Materials] (Box 63)
    - Bliwise, Robert J. [Duke Magazine] (Box 63)
    - Bloch, Edmond C. [Anesthesiology; Pediatrics] (Box 63)
    - Block, Martin (Box 63)
    - Bloom, Claudia [Institute of the Arts; Music] (Box 63)
    - Bloomer, Sherman Harrison [Geology] (Box 63)
    - Blue, Dan (Box 63)
    - Blum, Jacob Joseph [Physiology] (Box 63)
    - Blumenthal, James [Psychiatry; Medicine] (Box 63)
    - Blumfelder, Theresa [Hematology and Medical Oncology, Ambulatory Care Services] (Box 63)
    - Boadu, Fred Kofi [Civil Engineering] (Box 64)
    - Board, John A. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 64)
    - Boatwright, Mary Taliaferro [Classical Studies] (Box 64)
    - Bogdonoff, Morton David (Box 64)
    - Bohs, Lynn Allison [Botany] (Box 64)
    - Bolich, William Bryan [Law], d.1/21/1977 (Box 64)
    - Bollinger, Ralph R. [Thoracic Surgery; Immunology] (Box 64)
    - Bolognesi, Dani Paul [General and Thoracic Surgery] (Box 64)
    - Bonar, Robert A. [Biophysics, Surgery] (Box 64)
    - Bonaventura, Joseph [Biomedical Center; Marine Lab] (Box 64)
    - Bone, Allan H. [Music], d. 8/18/1992 (Box 64)
    - Boneau, C. Alan, d. 1993 (Box 64)
    - Bonk, James Frederick [Chemistry] (Box 64)
    - Bookhout, Cazlyn G. [Marine Lab] (Box 64)
    - Bookhout, Elizabeth C. [Physical Education] (Box 64)
    - Boomer, Walter E. (Box 64)
    - Boone, Charles Chaffin [DUMC] (Box 64)
    - Boothby, Neil (Box 64)
    - Borchardt, Frank J. [German Lang. and Lit.] (Box 64)
    - Borstelmann, Lloyd Joseph [Psychology], Retired 9/1/1987 (Box 64)
    - Bost, Louise E. [Oncology Recreation Therapy ] (Box 64)
    - Botwinick, Jack [Medical Psychology] (Box 64)
    - Boudreau, Alan Ernest [Geology] (Box 64)
    - Boulding, William F. [Fuqua] (Box 64)
    - Boustany, Rose Mary [Pediatric Neurology] (Box 64)
    - Bowden, William Anton, Jr. (Box 64)
    - Bowers, Henry Franklin, Jr. [Manager of Operations] (Box 64)
    - Bowers, Nancy (Box 64)
    - Bowie, James D. [Radiology; Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 64)
    - Boyarsky, Saul (Box 64)
    - Boyce, Stephen G. [Forestry] (Box 64)
    - Boyd, John L. [ Cardiology, Pediatrics] (Box 64)
    - Boyle, James [Law] (Box 64)
    - Boyle, Thomas A. [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 64)
    - Boyle, William [Immunology] (Box 64)
    - Boynton, John Ellswood [Botany] (Box 64)
    - Braboy-Jackson, Pamela [Sociology] (Box 64)
    - Bradford, William Dalton [Pathology] (Box 64)
    - Bradley, David Gilbert (Box 64)
    - Bradley, Don W. [Community and Family Medicine] (Box 64)
    - Bradley, Michael H. [Fuqua] (Box 64)
    - Bradshaw, Michael James [Admissions] (Box 64)
    - Bradhser, Charles K. [Chemistry] (Box 64)
    - Brady, David J. [Addy of Electrical and Computer Engineering] (Box 64)
    - Brady, Robert E. [Duke News Services] (Box 64)
    - Braibanti, Ralph [Political Science], Retired 9/1/1990 (Box 64)
    - Brandon, Debra Huffman [Nursing] (Box 64)
    - Brandon, Robert N. [Philosophy] (Box 64)
    - Branscomb, Harvie [Divinity], d. 1998 (Box 64)
    - Brantley, Bert Alton, Jr. (Box 64)
    - Braswell, Charles Marion (Box 64)
    - Brauer, Ralph Werner (Box 64)
    - Brazzel, Debra [D.U. Chapel; Religious Life ] (Box 64)
    - Bredenhoeft, Steven J. [Surgery] (Box 64)
    - Breeden, Douglas T. [Fuqua] (Box 64)
    - Brehm, Jack Williams [Psychology] (Box 64)
    - Brehm, John J. [Political Science] (Box 64)
    - Breitfeld, Philip [Pediatrics in Hematology-oncology] (Box 64)
    - Brenckman, Wayne D., Jr. [Hematology and Med. Oncology] (Box 64)
    - Breslin, Marianne S. [Psychiatry] (Box 64)
    - Bressler, Richard [Psychiatry] (Box 64)
    - Briner, William H. [Imaging, Radiology; Nuclear Med. Lab and Radiopharmacy] (Box 64)
    - Brinkhous, John R. [Compensation] (Box 64)
    - Brinkley, Roberta Florence [English; Woman's College], d. 6/1967 (Box 64)
    - Brizel, David M. [DUMC] (Box 64)
    - Brock, Dorothy Pendle [Endowment Administration] (Box 64)
    - Brock, Philip [Economics] (Box 64)
    - Brockett, Clyde W. [Music] (Box 64)
    - Broder, David (Box 64)
    - Broderson, Robert M. [Art] (Box 64)
    - Brodie, H. Keith H. [Addresses, Speeches, and Statements], 1985 - 1991 (Box 65)
    - Brodie, H. Keith H. [Articles], 1970-1999 (Box 65)
    - Brodie, H. Keith H. [Bios, Vitae, and Photos] (Box 65)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Martin [Economics], d. 6/2/1997 (Box 65)
    - Brough, Regina [Institute for Policy Sciences and Public Affairs ] (Box 65)
    - Broughton, Annie Leigh [Freshman Women] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Ann J. [Endochronology] (Box 65)
    - Brown, April S. [Electrical and Computer Engineering] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Charlotte Vestal [Art] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Earl I., II [J/A. Jones Civil Engineering] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Frances Campbell [Emerita, Chemistry], d. 10/14/1994 (Box 65)
    - Brown, Frank Clyde (Box 65)
    - Brown, Burdeen Fred [C.O.O. DUMC], d. 1/30/1993 (Box 65)
    - Brown, Harry Elton [DUMC] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Haywood [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Ivan W., Jr. (Box 65)
    - Brown, James Trig [General Medicine] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Leslie [Research Asst., History] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Montague [Health Administration] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Myrtle Irene [Nursing] (Box 65)
    - Brown, Ray Everett [of Hospital Administration] (Box 65)
    - Browning, Iley B. "Trip" [Pulmonary Div., Pediatrics] (Box 65)
    - Brownlee, William H. [of Old Testament, Divinity School] (Box 65)
    - Brummett, Paul O. [Material Support] (Box 65)
    - Brundage, Dorothy J. [Emerita, Nursing] (Box 65)
    - Bruno, Dieter [Surgery] (Box 65)
    - Bruzelius, Caroline Astrid [Art and Art History] (Box 65)
    - Bryan, Anne-Marie [Emerita, Romance Languages], Retired 9/1/1990 (Box 65)
    - Bryan, Edward H. [Civil Engineering] (Box 65)
    - Bryan, Joseph McKinley [Philanthropist], d. 4/1995 (Box 65)
    - Bryan, Paul [Music] (Box 65)
    - Bryan, Virginia S. [Woman's College], Retired 2/28/1987 (Box 65)
    - Bryant, Robert L. [Mathematics] (Box 65)
    - Bryers, James David [Civil and Environmental Engineering] (Box 65)
    - Bryson, Edwin Constant [Vice President and General Counsel], d. 4/20/1999 (Box 65)
    - Bryson, Judge Thaddeus Dillard [Law], d. 8/28/1950 (Box 65)
    - Buckley, Charles Edward, III [Allergy and Respiratory Diseases] (Box 65)
    - Buckley, Rebecca Hatcher [Allergy and Immunology, Pediatrics; Microbiology and Immunology] (Box 65)
    - Budd, Louis John [English] (Box 65)
    - Buehler, Albert George [Track Coach; Physical Education] (Box 65)
    - Buettner-Janusch, John [Primate Center] (Box 65)
    - Bufkin, Je Harned [Medical Record Library] (Box 65)
    - Bugg, Everett I. [Orthopedic Surgery] (Box 65)
    - Bulger, Roger J. [Allied Health Sciences] (Box 65)
    - Bullock, S. Elizabeth "Betty" [Music] (Box 65)
    - Bumbalough, Paul [Office of Student Development] (Box 65)
    - Burdick, Donald Smiley [Mathematics] (Box 65)
    - Burford, Walter (Box 65)
    - Burger, James [Arts and Sciences of Statistics] (Box 65)
    - Burger, Paula [Vice Provost for Academic Services] (Box 65)
    - Burger, Peter [Pathology] (Box 65)
    - Burger, Robert M. (Box 65)
    - Burgess, Mary (Box 66)
    - Burgess, Wade William (Box 66)
    - Burian, Peter H. [Classical Studies] (Box 66)
    - Burk, Lawrence [Radiology] (Box 66)
    - Burke, James R. [Neurology] (Box 66)
    - Burke, Marian C. [Fuqua] (Box 66)
    - Burkholder, Peter M. [Pathology] (Box 66)
    - Burness, John [Sr. Vice Pres. for Public Affairs] (Box 66)
    - Burns, Barbara [Psych. and Behavioral Sciences] (Box 66)
    - Burton, Claude S. [Dermatology, Medicine] (Box 66)
    - Burton, Richard M. [Fuqua] (Box 66)
    - Busse, Ewald William [Psychiatry and Dean Effective 9/1/1987] (Box 66)
    - Butler, Joseph D. [Facility Planning], Retired 5/1985 (Box 66)
    - Butters, Ronald R. [English] (Box 66)
    - Butters, Tom A. [Athletic Director] (Box 66)
    - Buzzard, Gale Herbert, II [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 66)
    - Byers, Michael [Law] (Box 66)
    - Byrd, Robert L. [David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library] (Box 66)
    - Byrne, William L. (Box 66)
    - Cadell, Elinor [Nursing] (Box 66)
    - Cady, Edwin Harrison [English] (Box 66)
    - Cahoon, John B., Jr. [Radiologic Technology] (Box 66)
    - Cahow, Clark R. [Registrar and of Admissions and Financial Aid] (Box 66)
    - Cairns, Michael [Infectious Diseases] (Box 66)
    - Caldwell, David S. [Rheumatology and Immunology] (Box 66)
    - Caldwell, Herschel [Football Coach; Coach, Freshman Football, Baseball, and Basketball] (Box 66)
    - Califf, Robert M. [Cardiology] (Box 66)
    - Callaway, J. Lamar [Dermatology], d. 1/19/1993 (Box 66)
    - Cameron, Edmund McCullough "Eddie" [Coach and Athletic Director], d. 11/25/1988 (Box 66)
    - Campbell, Dennis Marion [Divinity School] (Box 66)
    - Campbell, Ted Allen [Divinity School] (Box 66)
    - Campbell, Jerry Dean [University Librarian] (Box 66)
    - Campbell, Mary B. [Anesthesia] (Box 66)
    - Canent, Ramon V., Jr. [Cardiology] (Box 66)
    - Cannon, James, III [Divinity School] (Box 66)
    - Canon, David T. [Political Science] (Box 66)
    - Cant, Nell Beatty [Anatomy] (Box 66)
    - Canterbury, Alfrod K., Jr. [Aerospace Studies] (Box 66)
    - Cantor, Murray [Mathematics] (Box 66)
    - Carbone, Peter Francis, Jr. [Education] (Box 66)
    - Carin, Lawrence [Electrical Engineering] (Box 66)
    - Carl, Linda [Cultural Affairs] (Box 66)
    - Carlson, Alan [Ophthalmology] (Box 66)
    - Carlson, Cathy (Box 66)
    - Carmon, Ziv [Fuqua] (Box 66)
    - Caron, Marc G. [Cell Biology] (Box 66)
    - Carpenter, Dwight William [Physics] (Box 66)
    - Carrington, Paul DeWitt [Law] (Box 66)
    - Carroll, Barbara A. [Imaging, Radiology] (Box 66)
    - Carroll, Bernard J. [Psychiatry] (Box 66)
    - Carroll, Christopher R. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 66)
    - Carroll, Jackson W. [Ormond Center; Divinity School] (Box 66)
    - Carson, Culley C., III [Urology, Surgery] (Box 66)
    - Carson, Robert Charles [Psychiatry] (Box 66)
    - Carter, James Henry [Psychiatry] (Box 66)
    - Carter, Reginald D. [Clinical Physician's Program] (Box 66)
    - Cartmill, Matt [Departments of Anthropology and Anatomy] (Box 66)
    - Cartwright, William H. [Education] (Box 66)
    - Caserta, Ernesto Giuseppe [Romance Languages] (Box 67)
    - Casey, H. Craig [Electrical Engineering] (Box 67)
    - Casey, Patrick J. [Pharmacology and Cancer Biology] (Box 67)
    - Casseday, John H. "Pete" [Neurobiology] (Box 67)
    - Castriota, David [Art] (Box 67)
    - Cate, Thomas R. [Medicine] (Box 67)
    - Cato, Allen E. [Clinical Pediatrics] (Box 67)
    - Cavanaugh, G. S. Terrence [Trent Collection, Med. Ctr. Library; Medical Literature] (Box 67)
    - Cavanaugh, Patrick J. (Box 67)
    - Cavenar, Jesse O. [Psychiatry] (Box 67)
    - Cell, John W. [History], d. 10/26/2001 (Box 67)
    - Cerveris, Michael Edward [Institute of the Arts] (Box 67)
    - Chaddock, Jack Bartley [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 67)
    - Chafe, William [History; TCAS], 1970s-2000s (Box 67)
    - Chaiken, Leon Edward [Forestry Management] (Box 67)
    - Chamis, Anna Lisa, 2001 (Box 67)
    - Champagne, Mary [Nursing School] (Box 67)
    - Chandler, John Wesley [Univ. Board of Trustees] (Box 67)
    - Chao, Nelson [Medicine; Bone Marrow Transplant Program], 1998 (Box 67)
    - Chapman, Roger C. [Forest Biometrics], Appt. 9/1969 (Box 67)
    - Charles, Hal Cecil [Radiology] (Box 67)
    - Charlesworth, James H. [Religion] (Box 67)
    - Chase, Beatrice [Nursing], Retired 8/31/1989 (Box 67)
    - Chase, Jeffrey S. [Computer Science] (Box 67)
    - Chatrath, Prithijit [Curator, Primate Center] (Box 67)
    - Cheek, Dennis J. [Nursing] (Box 67)
    - Cheek, Roma S. [Political Science] (Box 67)
    - Cheifetz, Ira M. [Pediatrics] (Box 67)
    - Chen, Yuan-Tsong [Genetics and Metabolism, Pediatrics] (Box 67)
    - Cherny, Walter B. V. [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 67)
    - Cherpack, Clifton Cyril [Romance Languages] (Box 67)
    - Cherry, Robert Stephen [Mechanical and Biomedical Engineering] (Box 67)
    - Chesnut, Donald Blair [Chemistry ], (Effective 1/1/1999) (Box 67)
    - Childs, Benjamin Guy [Education] (Box 67)
    - Childs, Carol [Dance Program] (Box 67)
    - Childs, Jack Stith (Box 67)
    - Childs, Sue (Box 67)
    - Ching, Leo [Asian and African Language and Literature] (Box 67)
    - Chiorazzi, Michael G. [Law Library] (Box 67)
    - Chowdhury, Shyamal [Computer Science] (Box 67)
    - Christakos, Arthur Chris [Obstetrics and Gynecology; Medical Education] (Box 67)
    - Christensen, Norman Leroy [Forestry; Angier B. Duke Scholarship Program] (Box 67)
    - Christian, Charles Donald [Obstetrics and Gynecology; Division of Gynecologic Endocrinology] (Box 67)
    - Christian, Charles, II [Anesthesiology] (Box 67)
    - Christie, George C. [Law] (Box 67)
    - Christmas, William A. [Student Health Services ] (Box 67)
    - Chua, Amy L. [Law] (Box 67)
    - Cianciola, George [Medical Research Prof.] (Box 67)
    - Ciompi, Giorgio [Music. Ciompi Quartet] (Box 67)
    - Clack, Ronald James [CAPS; Interim Student Affairs (effective 7/1/2000)] (Box 67)
    - Clapp, James Robert [Medicine; Vice Chancellor, DUMC] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Bobby Wayne [University Relations] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Elizabeth Ann [Religion] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Elon Henry [Medical Art], d. 1/19/2001 (Box 67)
    - Clark, Henry Baisley [Religion] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Howard G., III [Biomedical and Biochemical Engineering] (Box 67)
    - Clark, James S. [Botany] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Kenneth Willis [Divinity School] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Peter Barton [Economics] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Reese Hunter [Pediatrics] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Robert E. [Dermatologic Surgery and Cutaneous Oncology] (Box 67)
    - Clark, Romane Lewis [Philosophy] (Box 67)
    - Clarke, Austin Chesterfield [Black Studies] (Box 67)
    - Clarke, George Elliott [English and Canadian Studies] (Box 67)
    - Clarke-Pearson, Daniel [Gynecologic Oncology] (Box 67)
    - Clavien, Pierre-Alain [General Surgery] (Box 67)
    - Clay, Diskin [Classical Studies] (Box 67)
    - Clay, Russell Travis [Duke News Service] (Box 67)
    - Claytor, Robert Brown [Divinity School; Chaplain, Med. Center] (Box 67)
    - Clegg, Scott T. [Radiology] (Box 67)
    - Cleaveland, Frederic N. [Political Science ], Effective 9/1/1985 (Box 68)
    - Cleland, James T. [Duke Univ. Chapel; Divinity School], d. 11/14/1978 (Box 68)
    - Cleland, William [Pediatrics], 2001 (Box 68)
    - Clements, Fiona Marshall [Anesthesiology] (Box 68)
    - Clifford, Edward [Medical Psychology and Research] (Box 68)
    - Clifford, Paul [Pre-Columbian Art Collection], Retired 12/1981 (Box 68)
    - Clippinger, Frank W., Jr. [Orthopedic Surgery; Rehabilitation Center] (Box 68)
    - Clotfelter, Charles T. [Public Policy; Economics], 1980-2001 (Box 68)
    - Clotfelter, James [Political Science] (Box 68)
    - Clough, Gerald Wayne [Engineering] (Box 68)
    - Clower, Virginia L. [Psychiatry; Clinical Division of Child Psychiatry] (Box 68)
    - Clubbe, John Louis Edwin [English] (Box 68)
    - Clum, John MacKenzie [English; Drama], 1960s-2000 (Box 68)
    - Clyde, Paul Hibbert [Far East History], d. 5/1/1998 (Box 68)
    - Coats, A. W. (Box 68)
    - Cobb, Frederick R. [Cardiology; Radiology] (Box 68)
    - Cobo, L. Michael [Ophthalmology] (Box 68)
    - Coburn, Andrew S. [Earth and Ocean Sciences], 2001 (Box 68)
    - Cochran, George [Center on Law and Poverty] (Box 68)
    - Cocks, Franklin Hadley [Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science] (Box 68)
    - Cocowitch, Harry M. [Naval Science Dept.], Retired 7/1/1972 (Box 68)
    - Coder, David [Philosophy] (Box 68)
    - Coffey, Charles Edward [Psychiatry] (Box 68)
    - Coffman, Thomas M. [Medicine] (Box 68)
    - Cohn, Jonathan A. [Medicine, Cell Biology] (Box 68)
    - Cohen, Harvey Jay [Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development] (Box 68)
    - Cohen, Kalman J. [Fuqua] (Box 68)
    - Cohen, Louis David [Psychology], Resigned 1962 (Box 68)
    - Cohen, Sanford I. [Psychiatry] (Box 68)
    - Coie, John David [Psychology] (Box 68)
    - Coker, Jerry [Music] (Box 68)
    - Cole, T. Boyce [Otolaryngology, Surgery] (Box 68)
    - Coleman, Dorian Lambelet [Law] (Box 68)
    - Coleman, Edward [Radiology], 2001 (Box 68)
    - Coleman, James E., Jr. [Law], 2001 (Box 68)
    - Coleman, Ralph Edward [Radiology; Nuclear Medicine] (Box 68)
    - Coleman, Rosalind A. [Genetics and Metabolism, Pediatrics; Biochemistry] (Box 68)
    - Coles, Robert [Institute of Political Science and Public Affairs] (Box 68)
    - Coles, Romand [Political Science] (Box 68)
    - Collins, Daniel W. [Fuqua] (Box 68)
    - Collins, Jeffrey Jay [Experimental Surgery, Microbiology and Immunology] (Box 68)
    - Collins, Leslie M. [Electrical and Computer Engineering] (Box 68)
    - Collins, Sheila [Psychiatry and Pharmacology] (Box 68)
    - Colton, Joel [History] (Box 68)
    - Colver, Robert Merle [Education] (Box 68)
    - Colvin, O. Michael [Medicine; Cancer Research; Comprehensive Cancer Center] (Box 68)
    - Conant, Norman F. [Microbiology], d. 4/1984 (Box 68)
    - Conaway, Mark R. [Biometry Division] (Box 68)
    - Conners, Carmen Keith [Medical Psychology, Psychiatry] (Box 68)
    - Connery, Robert H. [Political Science] (Box 68)
    - Connolly, John L., Jr. [Art] (Box 68)
    - Connor, W. Robert [Classical Studies; National Humanities Center] (Box 68)
    - Conover, Christopher [Public Policy] (Box 68)
    - Conrad, Cecilia [Economics] (Box 68)
    - Conrad, Robert Franklin [Economics] (Box 68)
    - Constanzo, Philip R. [Psychology] (Box 69)
    - Cook, Philip Jackson [Economics and Public Policy] (Box 69)
    - Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1993 (Box 69)
    - Cook, Wesley A. [Neurosurgery] (Box 69)
    - Cook-Degan, Robert M. (Box 69)
    - Cooke, Miriam [Asian and African Languages], 2001 (Box 69)
    - Coombs, John W. "Jack" [Baseball] (Box 69)
    - Coon, Susan L. [Cultural Affairs] (Box 69)
    - Cooney, James P. (Box 69)
    - Coonrad, Raphael W. "Ralph" [DUMC] (Box 69)
    - Cooper, A. Derwin (Box 69)
    - Cooper, Gregory J. [Philosophy] (Box 69)
    - Cooper, Sherri [NSOE], 1998 (Box 69)
    - Cooper, Walter G. [Commanding Officer, V-12], d. 9/1991 (Box 69)
    - Corbin, Charlotte [Alumnae Affairs] (Box 69)
    - Cordle, Thomas H. [Romance Languages] (Box 69)
    - Corey, Gordon Ralph (Box 69)
    - Corless, Joseph M. [Cell Biology] (Box 69)
    - Corless, Roger [Religion] (Box 69)
    - Corliss, Bruce H. [Geology] (Box 69)
    - Corrie, Bruce A. [Lacrosse] (Box 69)
    - Costello, Elizabeth [Psychiatry and Behav. Sciences] (Box 69)
    - Costello, Martin J. [Anatomy] (Box 69)
    - Costlow, John D. [Marine Lab], 1 of 4 (Box 69)
    - Cotton, Peter B. [Gastroenterology] (Box 69)
    - Counce, Sheila [Anatomy] (Box 69)
    - Coury, Louis A., Jr. [Chemistry] (Box 69)
    - Covi, Dario (Box 69)
    - Cox, Boyce Vernon (Box 70)
    - Cox, Craig [Fuqua] (Box 70)
    - Cox, Edwin B. [Hematology and Med. Oncology] (Box 70)
    - Cox, Elizabeth (Box 70)
    - Cox, James D. [Law] (Box 70)
    - Cox, Ralph Merritt (Box 70)
    - Cox, Richard L. [Residential Life] (Box 70)
    - Cox, Robert Calvin (Box 70)
    - Craig, William David [Captain, Eastward] (Box 70)
    - Craighead, W. Edward [Psychology] (Box 70)
    - Crane, Robert Dickson [Space Research Institute] (Box 70)
    - Crane, Robert I. [Asian Studies] (Box 70)
    - Crapo, James D. (Box 70)
    - Crawford, Jeffrey [Hematology and Med. Oncology] (Box 70)
    - Creasman, William T. [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 70)
    - Crellin, John K. [Medical History] (Box 70)
    - Crenshaw, James L. [Divinity School] (Box 70)
    - Crenshaw, Roy Neil, Jr. [Surgical PDC] (Box 70)
    - Crepeau, Elaine M. [Law Library] (Box 70)
    - Crisson, Stan [Football] (Box 70)
    - Crocker, Jon Christopher [Anthropology] (Box 70)
    - Crolla, Dominic [Medical Reporter, Information Services ] (Box 70)
    - Cromer, John A. [Anesthesiology] (Box 70)
    - Crossland, Kathryn M. [Nursing] (Box 70)
    - Crovitz, Elaine [Medical Psychology] (Box 70)
    - Crovitz, Herbert F. [Psychology] (Box 70)
    - Crowder. Larry [Marine Sciences] (Box 70)
    - Crowley, Thomas [NSOE], 2001 (Box 70)
    - Crowell, John Franklin [President, Trinity College (1857-1931)] (Box 70)
    - Crum, Mason [Biblical Literature] (Box 70)
    - Crumbliss, Alvin [Chemistry] (Box 70)
    - Culberson, William L. [Botany] (Box 70)
    - Cullen, Brian R. [Microbiology] (Box 70)
    - Cullins, Maureen D. (Box 70)
    - Culp, Jerome M. [Law] (Box 70)
    - Culver, Charles Marriott [Psychology] (Box 70)
    - Cunningham, Bruce [Registrar] (Box 70)
    - Curry, John F. [Psychiatry] (Box 70)
    - Cusson, Ronald Y. [Physics] (Box 70)
    - Cuttino, John Tindal [Pathology] (Box 70)
    - Cuyler, W. Kenneth [Obstetrics] (Box 70)
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 70)
    - Dai, Bingham [Psychology] (Box 70)
    - D'Amico, Thomas, 1999 (Box 70)
    - Daniels, Boyd L. [Religion] (Box 70)
    - Daniels, Frederick William, III [Admissions] (Box 70)
    - Daniels, Frederick H. [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 70)
    - Daniels-Race, Theda [Electrical Engineering] (Box 70)
    - Dankel, Thaddeus George, Jr. [Mathematics] (Box 70)
    - Danner, Richard A. [Law Library] (Box 70)
    - Darkis, Frederick Randolph [Chemistry] (Box 70)
    - Darrow, Daniel C. [Pediatrics] (Box 70)
    - David, Ellen [Theology] (Box 70)
    - Davidson, Cathy N. [English] (Box 70)
    - Davidson, Charles J. [Cardiology] (Box 70)
    - Davidson, H. Clint [Human Resources] (Box 70)
    - Davidson, Eugene A. [Biochemistry] (Box 70)
    - Davidson, Harry [Duke University Orchestra] (Box 70)
    - Davidson, Jonathan [Psychiatry] (Box 70)
    - Davies, David G. (Box 70)
    - Davies, William David (Box 70)
    - Davis, Calvin D. [History] (Box 70)
    - Davis, Gifford [Romance Languages], d.7/18/1984 (Box 70)
    - Davis, James E. [Surgery] (Box 70)
    - Davis, James Norman [Neurology/Pharmacology] (Box 70)
    - Davis, Morgan [Math/Physics] (Box 70)
    - Davis, N. Gregson G. [Classical Studies] (Box 70)
    - Davis, R. Duane [Thoracic Surgery] (Box 70)
    - Davis, Richard [History] (Box 70)
    - Dawson, Jeffrey R. [Immunology] (Box 70)
    - Dawson, Mary [Librarian] (Box 70)
    - Dawson, Robert E. [Ophthalmology] (Box 70)
    - Day, Eugene [Microbiology / Immunology] (Box 70)
    - Day, Ruth S. [Psychology] (Box 70)
    - Dearlove, Judith Elizabeth [English] (Box 70)
    - DeBruijn, Norbertus Paulus [Anesthesiology] (Box 70)